sarcasmsociety.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Sarcasm Society

_Updated: June 16, 2014_

Your privacy is one of our biggest concerns. Occasionally [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) may change its privacy policy. [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) encourages visitors to check this page often to check for any changes to the privacy policy. Continued use of [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) websites upon modification to its privacy policy will act as your acceptance of any and all changes.

## Intro

[Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) puts your privacy at the top of our list of priorities.

This privacy policy was has been created in accordance with the privacy policy provided by wordpress.com(automattic.com) under the creative commons sharealike license.This notice is very important to any visitor of [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) and should be read thoroughly.

## Website Visitors and Registered Users

[Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) collects non-personally-identifying information in a matter similar to many website operators. Information that is typically collected include but are not limited to ones such as the referring site, date and time of visit, browser, operating system, and count of returning versus new visitors. [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) uses this information to get a better understanding of their audience and therefore better the website as a whole. [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) may publish information to the general public regarding the usage of its website and or affiliate websites but will not release personally-identifying information. Information such as IP addresses or other personally-identifying information may be collected but will not be used to acquire private information on its visitors, nor will it disclose any such information other than described below.

## Aggregation of Personally-Identifying Information

A number of visitors to [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) decide to interact with the website in a manner where personally-identifiable information is necessary. The amount or type of information that is required will depend upon the form of interaction. In every case, [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) will collect such information only as is required or deemed appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitors interaction with [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/). [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) does not disclose personally-identifying information other then as described below. Visitors have the ability to refuse to provide personally-identifiable information at the risk that they may be prevented from engaging in certain website-related activities.

## Aggregated Statistics

[Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) may analyze and collect statistics about the activities of visitors to its websites. For example, [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) may keep account of the most popular pages, collections, or referring sites. [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) may display this information publicly or share it with others. [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) does not release personally-identifiable information related to its statistics other then as described below.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifiable Information

[Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) shares potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to its employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know such information to process it on [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/)’s behalf or to provide services to [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/), and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose any such information to any other party except for those directly involved. Some of this potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information may be given to parties outside of your country; by using [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) websites, you acknowledge and consent to the transfer of such information to them. Also, in some cases we may decide to buy or sell assets. In this type of transaction, information is one of the business assets that is transferred. Additionally, if [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) or considerably all of its assets were acquired, or in the unfortunate event that [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) goes out of business or enteres bankruptcy, use information would be one of the assets that are transferred and or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that this type of transfer may occur, and that any acquirer of [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) may continue to use any personal and non-personal information only as set forth in this policy. Otherwise, [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) will not lease out, rent, or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Aside from its employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations, as explained in the previous paragraph, [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required by law to do so. [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) will also disclose such information when it believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the rights or property of [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/), third parties or the general public. Should you be a registered user of a [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) website and have supplied your email address, [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) may send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit feedback, and or keep you informed of whats happening with [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) and its services. If you send a request to [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) either privately or through one of the websites contact tools, [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) reserves the right to publish it in order to assist us in clarifying, respond to your request, or to help other users with the same issue. [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) ensures that all measures are taken that are reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration, or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. Please be aware that if you are submitting information to “chat rooms,” “forums,” “comments” or “message boards” such information is then considered public information. In other words, you lose any and all privacy rights you may have with regards to that information. Doing so also increases the amount of unwanted communications or SPAM.

## Cookies

A cookie is information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) uses cookies to help track and identify visitors, monitor the usage of [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) websites and website access preferences every time the visitor returns to the site. Should a visitor refuse to have cookies placed on their computers, will have to set their browsers to refuse cookies prior to using the [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) websites. Users acknowledge and accept that disabling cookies may cause certain features of [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) websites to not function properly.

## Advertisements

Ads that appear on any of [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may also set cookies. These cookies give the ad server the ability to recognize your computer every time they send you an online advertisement to put together information about you or anyone who uses your computer. This information allows the ad networks to, among other things, deliver advertisements targeted at the users interest. This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/), but does not cover any use of cookies by advertisers.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

## Third Party Links

This privacy policy applies only to [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) and the information that is collected by its websites. This privacy policy does not apply to the conduct of other companies that [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) does not own or control, or employees that [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) does not manage. [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) websites may contain or promote links to other websites. Any information that you provide to, or that is obtained by, third-party organizations or websites may be subject to the privacy policy of those sites, if any at all. Please read the privacy policy of any and all third-party websites you visit. It is the sole responsibility of these third parties to abide by any and all restrictions on the disclosure of your potentially-personally and personally-identifying information. [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) and its affiliates shall not be liable for any wrongful use or disclosure of your potentially-identifying and or personally-identifying information by any third party.

## Security

All non-personally-identifying information, potentially personally-identifying and personally identifying-information described above is stored on restricted database servers. [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) ensures that reasonable measures are taken to ensure the safety of such information. 

## Choice/Opt-out

If [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) contacts you by email concerning new products, services or information that you did not expressly request, [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) will provide you with an email address by which you may request no further notices. 

## Contact

If you have any questions or are unsure about something within the privacy policy, or the [Sarcasm Society](http://sarcasmsociety.com/) website itself, please contact us.
